Center for International Education and Global Strategy; Records ua550
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Overseas Academic Programs, 1965-1980; 10 cubic ft.
  - Nice Program, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Nice Program Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Nice Program, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Nice Program, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Nice Program, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Nice Program, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Nice Program, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Nice Program, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nice Program, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Nice Program Expenditures, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Nice Permanent File, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Exchange Students France, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Exchange Fellowships, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Postes D'Assistant, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Fellowships - invitational at SUNYA Students, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - French Scholar Program, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Publicity, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Nice Publicity, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Dr. Colman Nice Records, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Nice Registration, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nice, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Nice Students, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Nice Students, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Nice - Student Selection, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ritual Questionnaires from Nice Students, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Nice Revised Proposal, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Nice Students, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Transportation Ryndam to Nice + Ellinis, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Nice Trauel, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - PSLP Brochure, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pre Freshman Summer Language Program, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - PSLP German Directors Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - PSLP Committee, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PSLP France Chauvin, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Germany G.I Brochure, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PSLP Goethe Institute, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - PSLP Goethe Institute Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - PSLP Goethe Institute Munich, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Richard Hester G.I. Germany0, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - PSLP Italy, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Scholarship Forms Portugal, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - PSLP Portugal, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Spain, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - PSLP Evaluations, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - PSLP Credit Standing of Participants, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Final Trip Germany, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - PSLP Financing, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Forms Info Sheets PSLP, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - PSLP Medical Claim Forms, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Rome Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Rome Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Rome Correspondence General, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Rome Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Rome Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Rome Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Italy Rome John Falconieri, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - General Information Rome Program, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Rome Participants, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Rome Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Planning Rome, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Rome Program, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Printing Materials Rome Program, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - General Registration, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Rome Publicity, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Proposals Rome, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Rome Program, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Postes d'assistant, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - SUNYA Students Abroad, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, 1967-1971 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, 1967-1972 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Committee - SLAP, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - SLAP Info, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - SLAP Directory, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Committee - SLAP, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Committee - SLAP, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Cuernavaca, Mexico Site Descriptions, Undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - SLAP Directors Report, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - SLAP Directors, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - SLAP Directors, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - SLAP Info Letters, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - SLAP Site Visitation Austria, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - SLAP General, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - France Summer Language Broad Program, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - SLAP France, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Vacancies Administrative Applicants, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - SLAP France, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - SLAP France Director Correspondence, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Evaluations SLAP France, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - France Summer Evaluations, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - SLAP Program Evaluations France, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - SLAP France Info, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - France Site Description, Undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - SLAP France Travel, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Summer Language Abroad Program General, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - SLAP Germany, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - SLAP Germany, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - SLAP Germany, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - SLAP Germany Directors Correspondence, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - SLAP Germany Evaluations, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - SLAP Germany Evaluations, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - SLAP Germany Evaluations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - SLAP Germany - Goethe Institut, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - SLAP Germany Info, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Germany Site Description, Undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Summer Germany Tests, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - SLAP Germany Travel, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Goethe Institut Central Office Summer Language Abroad Program, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Guadalajara Evaluations, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Guadalajara Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Italy Summer Language Abroad Program, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - SLAP Italy, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - SLAP Italy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - SLAP Italy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - SLAP Italy, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - SLAP Italy Evaluations, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SLAP Italy Evaluations, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SLAP Italy info, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Italy Site Description, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SLAP Italy Travel, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Evaluations Rome, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SLAP Letters, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SLAP Portugal, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Portugal Evaluations, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SLAP Russia, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - SLAP Spain, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SLAP Spain, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - SLAP Spain, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - SLAP Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - SLAP Permanent File, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - SLAP Spain Directors Correspondence, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - SLAP Spain Evaluations, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Spain Summer Evaluations, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - SLAP Program Evaluations Spain, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - SLAP Spain Info, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - SLAP Site Description, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Spain Site Description, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - SLAP Spain Travel, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - SLAP Spain General, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - SLAP Italy General, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - SLAP Germany General, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - SLAP France General, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Travel - SLAP, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - SILPA Committee, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - SILPA Committee, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SILPA Directors, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - SILPA France Directors Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - France SILPA Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - SILPA France, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - SILPA France Generals, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - SILPA France Generals, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - SILPA France Info, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - SILPA France Travel, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Germany SILPA Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - SILPA Germany General, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - SILPA Germany General, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - SILPA Germany General, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - SILPA Germany Info, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - SILPA Italy General, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - SILPA Italy Info, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - SILPA Italy Travel, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - SILPA Spain General, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - SILPA Spain General, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - SILPA Spain Travel, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - SILPA Committee, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - SILPA Directors, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Italy SILPA Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - SILPA Italy Travel, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - SPAIN SILPA Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - SILPA Italy General, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - SILPA Spain Info, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - SILPA Spain General, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - SPINS Summer Program for International Students, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - S.P.I.N.S, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - SUNYA Japanese Program, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Russia, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Invitations dor Soviet Students, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Fitzpatrick, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Applicants Exchange, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Exchange Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Directors Correspondence, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Exchange Program, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Adjunct Instructions, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Orientation, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Soviet Students, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Adjunct Instructions, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Travel by Soviet Exchange Visitors, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Adjunct Instructions, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Moscow Thorez Institute Adjunct Instruction, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Field Trips, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Directors Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Moscow Thorez Institute Adviser SUNY, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Correspondence SUNY Program Adviser, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Field Trips, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Exchange Program, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - MGU Adviser's Correspondence, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - SUNY/MOSCOW Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - MGU Adviser SUNY, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - MGU Program, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - MGU Program, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - MGU Exchange Participants SUNY, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - MGU Program Travel, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - MGU Soviet Participants, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - MGU Participants - Soviet, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Latin American Area Studies Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Area Studies Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - State Meeting on F.L's, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - SUNY Meetings on Programs in Italy, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - SUNY Meetings on Japan, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Madrid Meeting on Spain and South America, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - SUNY Meetings on Programs in Puerto Rico, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - SUNY Meetings on Programs in Spain, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - SUNY Meetings on Programs in South America, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Meetings on Programs in United Kingdom, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Contract, Wurzburg and Nice, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Wurzburg Brochures, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Wurzburg Booklet Draft + Copy, Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Wurzburg Brochures, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wurzburg Budget, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Wurzburg Breakdown of Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Wurzburg Breakdown of Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Wurzuburg Allen Caswell, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Course Frequency List Wurburg, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - SUNY Oneonta Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Wurzburg SUNYA Oneonta Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Wurzburg SUNY Advisory Committee (Albany and Oneonta), 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Wurzburg SUNY Advisory Committee (Albany and Oneonta), 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Wurzburg SUNYA Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Wurzburg Caswell, Allen, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Committee Wurzburg, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wurzburg SUNYA Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wurzburg Directorial Report, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wurzburg Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Wurzburg Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Wurzburg Directors, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Wurzburg SUNY Advisory Committee (Albany and Oneonta), 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Wurzburg Directors Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Wurzburg Directors, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Wurzburg Directors Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations Wurzburg, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Wurzburg Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Wurzburg Evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Wurzburg Evaluations, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Questionnaires Wurzburg, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Wurzburg Exchange Professor, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Wurzburg Exchange Professor, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Wurzburg Exchange Professor, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Wurzburg Exchange Students, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Wurzburg Exchange Students, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Wurzburg Finances, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Wurzburg Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Wurzburg Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wurzburg Flight, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Wurzburg Goethe Insitut, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Wurzburg Brochures, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Forms Sent to Participants Wurburg, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Wurzburg General, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Wurzburg Goethe Insitut, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Wurzburg Goethe Insitut Grades, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Wurzburg Goethe Insitut, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Wurzburg Information Instructions, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Wurzburg Info, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Wurzburg Info Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Wurzburg Info, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Wurzburg Information, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Wurzburg Information, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Wurzburg Info, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Wurzburg Inquiries, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - ISWA Wurzburg, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Moore, Erna, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Wurzburg Program [1 of 2], 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Wurzburg Program [2 of 2], 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Wurzburg Proposal, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Participants Wurzburg, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Oneonta Participants Wurzburg, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Wurzburg Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Program, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Wurzburg Report Prof. Erna Moore, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - RL Richardson Wurzburg Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Status Report on SUNY Task Force on Israel Programs, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Wurzburg Selection, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Wurzburg Students Credits, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Wurzburg Withdrawals, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Wurzburg Evaluations Summer, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Wurzburg, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Wurzburg, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Wurzburg, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Wurzburg Participants, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Planning Wurzburg, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Wurzburg Presession, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Printing Wurzburg, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Wurzburg Presession, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Wurzburg Scholarship, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Wurzburg Test, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Wurzburg Program Adviser, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Wurzburg Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Wurzburg SUNY Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Wurzburg Program, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Administrative Files, 1967-1978; 7.53 cubic ft.
  Series is arranged in its original order.
  This series documents the management of the Office of International Programs itself as opposed to the programs it administered. It is primarily made up of correspondence and letter files kept by the Office as well as form letters sent to students interested in International Programs. It contains material related to SUNY-wide International Programs and conferences held with the Directors of other college and university international programs. The series also contains policy statements, program proposals and international program reports.
  - Office Letter File (700 - 934), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Office Letter File (435 - 699), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Office Letter File (1 - 434), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter File, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chron File, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chron File, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letter File, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reims, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee on International Programs, 19793 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Departmental Letter File, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Departmental Letter File, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo - Sienna, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Janet Sickles Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Departmental Letter File (782-1124), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Departmental Letter File (545 -781), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - D.I.E, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - OAP's, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee OAP's, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - OAP Advisory Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - OAP Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Committee International Education, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - OAP Advisory Committee Summary Notes, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Committee International Education, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Council Directors of International Programs Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - D.I.E Meetings Syracuse, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ESL Year Long Program, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Israel Advisory Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Soviet East Euro Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Program Proposals, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Printing, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Directors Handbook for Administering Student Affairs at Off Campus Locations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Forms for IEE, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Forms for IEE, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Camp Counselors in France and Spain, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Questionnaires on Overseas Program, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Program Evaluations, 19691973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Print Shop, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Printing, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Printing File, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Originals for Print Shop, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Print Shop Originals, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Printing Moscow, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Printing Non-Specific, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - John Cabot SUNYA Exchange Proposal, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Consortium on German Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Exchange and Staff, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - FAMES, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Meeting with Academic Deans CWC, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - President Committee on International Education, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Program Announcement SUNYA, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Promotion and Recruitment, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Questionnaire Instituto Italiano Di Cultura, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Report on Management Improvement Project Action, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Theatre SUNY meeting, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Whole World Handbook Questionnaires (CIEE), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - World Studies Data Bank Questionnaires, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Independent Students, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Students, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program General, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Wurzburg, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Questionnaires - State Education Department Dr. Osteen, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - OAP Alumni, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Franco-American Exchange, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Participants, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Participants, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico Exchange Program Participants, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - SPINS, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Richard Seltzer, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - USSR Inquiries, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Hebrew University, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - CIDOC-Cale Breakdown of Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Info Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Planning Program, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Info Letters Sent to all Programs, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - London Application form Extras, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - British Theatre Summer, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Summer Program for Japanese Students, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Guatemala, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - EOP Students Abroad, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Brockport General, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Brockport Aberdeen, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 40)